# **Pedro Scaff**

Software Engineer | Brazilian | pedro@scaff.me | Living in Berlin

### About me

I'm a full stack engineer with a broad range of skills. I can work with different technologies and learn fast. I have experience working with high quality standards and agile teams. I like setting up processes and helping teams work better and be more productive. I highly value a healthy and happy work environment.

I'm currently working as a software engineer at Vay. I'm the main responsible for the user interface that is used to remotely drive a car. I work both on the web app and on the embedded C++ part of the software. I setup the CI/CD for the web application and API including deployment to the cloud.

# **Experience**

#### Embedded Software Engineer at Vay | May 2020 - Current

- Development of real-time, low-latency application built using ROS and CEF running on Linux
- Lit Element/Redux/ThreeJS for Javascript WebApp
- Development of embedded/native part using C++
- IPC interface for communication between C++ and JS
- Infrastructure setup using Terraform

#### Software Engineer at Daimler Mobility Services | August 2019 – May 2020

- Backend development of on-demand fleet API
- · Distributed backend in Node.js with Kafka

#### Software Developer at Pixsy | October 2018 – July 2019

- Frontend development of WebApp using React / Redux
- Setup for test automation infrastructure (Jenkins, Docker)

#### Software Engineer at HERE Technologies | November 2017 - September 2018

- Frontend development of WebApps featuring 2D and 3D visualizations
- Node.js development of APIs tools and pipelines

#### Working student as a QA Engineer at HERE Technologies | January 2015 - October 2017

- Automation of functional tests for JS library and WebApp
- Manual testing of JS library API and WebApp
- Setup for test automation infrastructure (Jenkins, Docker)

#### Private language teacher (german) | July 2012 – July 2013

### **Education**

#### HTW Berlin - University of Applied Sciences | 2014 - 2017

• Computer Engineering, Bachelor

## **Skills**

- · Javascript / Typescript
- NodeJS
- AWS
- Terraform
- Rust
- C++

# Languages

• Mother language: Portuguese

• Fluent: English and German

• Basic: Spanish and Italian

### Social

- Github
- LinkedIn